const questionsDataHiraganaToRomaji = [
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "あ",
    answers: ["a", "i", "u", "e"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "い",
    answers: ["o", "u", "i", "e"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "う",
    answers: ["e", "u", "o", "a"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "え",
    answers: ["i", "u", "o", "e"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "お",
    answers: ["o", "a", "u", "i"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "か",
    answers: ["ka", "sa", "ta", "na"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "き",
    answers: ["ni", "shi", "chi", "ki"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "く",
    answers: ["ku", "su", "tsu", "nu"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "け",
    answers: ["se", "te", "ne", "ke"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "こ",
    answers: ["ko", "so", "to", "no"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "さ",
    answers: ["sa", "ta", "na", "ha"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "し",
    answers: ["shi", "chi", "ni", "hi"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "す",
    answers: ["su", "tsu", "nu", "fu"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "せ",
    answers: ["se", "te", "ne", "he"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "そ",
    answers: ["so", "to", "no", "ho"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "た",
    answers: ["ta", "da", "sa", "na"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ち",
    answers: ["chi", "shi", "ji", "ni"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "つ",
    answers: ["tsu", "su", "nu", "fu"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "て",
    answers: ["te", "de", "se", "ne"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "と",
    answers: ["to", "do", "no", "ho"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "な",
    answers: ["na", "ma", "ra", "ya"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "に",
    answers: ["ni", "mi", "ri", "ji"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ぬ",
    answers: ["nu", "mu", "ru", "yu"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ね",
    answers: ["ne", "me", "re", "he"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "の",
    answers: ["no", "mo", "ro", "yo"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "は",
    answers: ["ha", "ba", "pa", "ma"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ひ",
    answers: ["hi", "bi", "pi", "mi"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ふ",
    answers: ["fu", "bu", "pu", "mu"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "へ",
    answers: ["he", "be", "pe", "me"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ほ",
    answers: ["ho", "bo", "po", "mo"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ま",
    answers: ["ma", "na", "sa", "ra"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "み",
    answers: ["mi", "ni", "shi", "ri"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "む",
    answers: ["mu", "nu", "su", "ru"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "め",
    answers: ["me", "ne", "se", "re"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "も",
    answers: ["mo", "no", "so", "ro"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "や",
    answers: ["ya", "ma", "ra", "wa"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ゆ",
    answers: ["yu", "mu", "ru", "fu"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "よ",
    answers: ["yo", "mo", "ro", "to"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ら",
    answers: ["ra", "la", "ya", "wa"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "り",
    answers: ["ri", "li", "yi", "wi"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "る",
    answers: ["ru", "lu", "yu", "wu"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "れ",
    answers: ["re", "le", "ye", "we"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ろ",
    answers: ["ro", "lo", "yo", "wo"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "わ",
    answers: ["wa", "ra", "ya", "pa"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "を",
    answers: ["wo", "ro", "yo", "po"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "text",
    question: "ん",
    answers: ["n", "m", "nn", "nm"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
];

export { questionsDataHiraganaToRomaji };

const questionsDataHiraganaAudio = [
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "あ",
    answers: ["あ", "い", "う", "え"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "い",
    answers: ["お", "う", "い", "え"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "う",
    answers: ["え", "う", "お", "あ"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "え",
    answers: ["い", "う", "お", "え"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "お",
    answers: ["お", "あ", "う", "い"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "か",
    answers: ["か", "さ", "た", "な"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "き",
    answers: ["に", "し", "ち", "き"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "く",
    answers: ["く", "す", "つ", "ぬ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "け",
    answers: ["せ", "て", "ね", "け"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "こ",
    answers: ["こ", "そ", "と", "の"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "さ",
    answers: ["さ", "た", "な", "は"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "し",
    answers: ["し", "ち", "に", "ひ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "す",
    answers: ["す", "つ", "ぬ", "ふ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "せ",
    answers: ["せ", "て", "ね", "へ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "そ",
    answers: ["そ", "と", "の", "ほ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "た",
    answers: ["た", "だ", "さ", "な"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ち",
    answers: ["ち", "し", "じ", "に"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "つ",
    answers: ["つ", "す", "ぬ", "ふ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "て",
    answers: ["て", "で", "せ", "ね"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "と",
    answers: ["と", "ど", "の", "ほ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "な",
    answers: ["な", "ま", "ら", "や"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "に",
    answers: ["に", "み", "り", "じ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ぬ",
    answers: ["ぬ", "む", "る", "ゆ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ね",
    answers: ["ね", "め", "れ", "へ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "の",
    answers: ["の", "も", "ろ", "よ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "は",
    answers: ["は", "ば", "ぱ", "ま"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ひ",
    answers: ["ひ", "び", "ぴ", "み"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ふ",
    answers: ["ふ", "ぶ", "ぷ", "む"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "へ",
    answers: ["へ", "べ", "ぺ", "め"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ほ",
    answers: ["ほ", "ぼ", "ぽ", "も"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ま",
    answers: ["ま", "な", "さ", "ら"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "み",
    answers: ["み", "に", "し", "り"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "む",
    answers: ["む", "ぬ", "す", "る"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "め",
    answers: ["め", "ね", "せ", "れ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "も",
    answers: ["も", "の", "そ", "ろ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "や",
    answers: ["や", "ま", "ら", "わ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ゆ",
    answers: ["ゆ", "む", "る", "ふ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "よ",
    answers: ["よ", "も", "ろ", "と"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ら",
    answers: ["ら", "わ", "や", "ま"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "り",
    answers: ["り", "い", "し", "ち"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "る",
    answers: ["る", "う", "す", "つ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "れ",
    answers: ["れ", "え", "せ", "て"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ろ",
    answers: ["ろ", "お", "と", "こ"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "わ",
    answers: ["わ", "ら", "や", "た"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "を",
    answers: ["を", "お", "よ", "と"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    type: "audio",
    question: "ん",
    answers: ["ん", "あん", "いん", "うん"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
];

export { questionsDataHiraganaAudio };
